steadyhealth.com 2017-06-24

# SteadyHealth.com

  * About Us
  * Medical Team
  * Terms of Use
  * Privacy Policy
  * Advertising Policy
  * FAQ

SteadyHealth.com is firmly committed to Your privacy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, SteadyHealth.com, as well as any other software or services we provide through site (e.g. SteadyHealth Facebook App).

The protection of your privacy is very important to us, given the nature of health oriented online community, so this is why we have adopted the following practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information.

## Security and Liability

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. This site maintains a dedicated server with restricted access only to authorized user accounts.

The webmaster, administrator and moderators cannot be held responsible if data integrity on the site becomes compromised. While we cannot guarantee that no accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use of your information will occur, we try to prevent such occurrences.

## Children Privacy

SteadyHealh is not intended for use by the children under the age of 13. We will not collect any personally identifiable information from anyone we know is a child under the age of 13, or allow them to participate on SteadyHealth discussion boards.

If we become aware that person under the age of 13 has submitted personal information or any other form of content to SteadyHealth, that becomes a reason for immediate account suspension, without any prior notice.

## Privacy in Public

Any information disclosed on the SteadyHealth Discussion Boards or comments, replies in other sections becomes public information. We advise you to keep in mind that all discussion board posts are subject to search engines with world-wide access to any reader. Do not post or offer your real name, email address, home address, telephone number, or any other contact information.

Email addresses can attract spammers that are difficult to control. If you want to exchange your personal contact information with other members, please use our Private Messaging system. But we strongly advise you against any form of sharing personal information with people you have only met online.

We also recommend that you do not register your real name, your unique email address, or the name of a website, as a potential username. In case you decide to post some for you personally embarrassing or sensitive content, in order to seek help or share information, please consider that even using your casual username which could be interconnected indirectly with you by your friends and family. The best practice is to use username that cannot be linked to you.

Keep your username anonymous.

Information including, but not limited to, email addresses, mailing addresses, telephone numbers, names, websites or links, personal profile settings, signature, posts, surveys, polls, private messages, websites, and research studies will be removed without any prior notice, as defined in our Terms of Use.

## What Information do you Gather Automatically from Visitors?

We use your IP address (the series of numbers associated with your individual computer) to help us maintain our site and identify problems with our server. Your IP address does not disclose any personally revealing information about you.

We do use cookies to identify traffic that comes through advertising and to facilitate a more user friendly experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site places on your computer's hard drive so we know it's you when you visit. This helps us to create a personalized experience for you when you visit our site. The use of cookies is a very common practice on the Internet. If you are uncomfortable with this, you can disable all cookies through your browser settings. Your enjoyment of our site won't be affected if you have set your browser to reject cookies.

## What Information Will you Ask me for?

When you register to use any SteadyHealth.com website or specific service, you will be asked for some general identifying information which will enable us to provide you with this individualized service. Should you choose to register to our site using SteadyHealth Facebook App, we collect only the basic personal information you made available in your Facebook Account Privacy Settings.

We gather contact information (like your email address), demographic information (like your city of residence or age). We may share some of this information for our own research purposes with our professional advisors or consultants and third party partners. However, the shared information will be limited to non-personally identifying demographic information shared under cover of a confidentiality agreement. We will only use this information in the course of providing our service to you.

Once you have registered, you will be given the option of editing of your profile (personal description, password and contact information).

SteadyHealth does not send promotional or commercial emails to its users without permission. SteadyHealth may email its users periodically to inform them about the status of the website or of upcoming changes to the site, and for feedback on satisfaction questionnaires. Additionally, we inform users about changes to our privacy policy via email.

## SteadyHealth.com Facebook App Privacy

Steadyhealth.com may collect any Facebook Information you have made visible to "Everyone" on Facebook, as well as the information Facebook designates as your publicly available information, possibly including your name, profile picture, gender, e-mail address, birthday, websites, networks, list of friends or any other information you’ve made public.

To protect your personally identifiable information once you login on SteadyHealth.com, you will be automatically offered an option to “anonymize” your username. This means your real Facebook name and profile picture will not appear across Discussion Boards or in the comments section.

You may change your Information, including your name and profile picture, in your profile settings on the Steadyhealth.com site at any time.

### How will we use your Information

Steadyhealth.com will only use information assotieted with your Facebook account for the following purposes:

  * to enable you to use the Steadyhealth.com site
  * to enable you to share content posted on Steadyhealth.com site on the Facebook
  * to periodically send emails to you on the email address you have provided, if you opt-in to receive them

### Links to other websites

Steadyhealth.com Apps may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should be aware that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

### Your privacy rights and choices

You may stop the Steadyhealth.com from using your Information at any time by uninstalling the Steadyhealth Facebook Application through your Facebook account. Keep in mind that you will still have to follow the procedure for SteadyHealth account removal, as defined in our [Terms of Service](http://www.steadyhealth.com/polices/registration-terms/).

## How Will this Information be Used and Who has Access to it?

If you choose to have them sent to you, we may use your contact information to send you valuable updates and timely notices of promotions and mailbox status reports. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt-in to receiving different types of communications from us at the point where we request registration information. You may modify this choice at any time by selecting "Profile" from the top user menu. We reserve the right to use your contact information at any time to advise you of any updates that may materially affect your rights or status on our site.

Your non-personally identifying demographic information is used to personalize your experience, allow other members to find you through a search, to compose your personal profile - which is associated with a pseudonymous identity you have created (username). Your contact information are available to other members only if you pre-set this options, otherwise our default setting will allow other users to see your contact information only, without demographic characteristics. Non-registered users (visitors) have ability to send you personal message but they are not able to see your contact information until they subscribe and become a valid SteadyHealth.com community member. In the event that you decide to buy one of our products or services, you will be asked for your financial information (like credit card number) which cannot be read by others when you initiate your order through a secured system.

The specific information we collect is not shared with other organizations and we will never release your personally identifiable information to an external organization without your prior consent except for the purposes of validating credit information and collecting debts.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by operation of law, which may include, but is not limited to a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on SteadyHealth.com.

Although SteadyHealth.com makes use of up to date technology in order to protect your pictures, audio and video recordings from being copied or captured by unauthorized third parties, please keep in mind that we cannot ensure complete protection.

## Who Will be Able to See my SteadyHealth User Profile?

All the information you submit on your user profile, such as username, avatar, date of birth, online status or your activity on SteadyHealth.com is completely under your control. In your profile settings, Profile Privacy control enables you to make your profile visible only to the registered members, or to keep the information completely private.

SteadyHealth Administrators will only override the privacy setting you’ve chosen in case there is potential breach of [Terms of Service](http://www.steadyhealth.com/polices/registration-terms/).

## Email Notifications

SteadyHealth does not send promotional or commercial emails to its users without permission or prior terms compliance. SteadyHealth may email its users periodically to inform them about the status of the website or of upcoming changes to the site, and for feedback on satisfaction questionnaires.

Additionally, we inform users about changes to our privacy policy via email.

Your email address may also be used to confirm your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one).

Further, SteadyHealth may email a user at any time regarding issues with his/her account.

Confidential, private or semi-private information included in the content of emails received from or sent to you will not be disclosed to anyone at any time unless required by law.

## How Long do You Keep the Information I've given You?

We keep the information you have given us for as long as you are a member on the site or for as long as we are required to do so by law, whichever is longer.

## Can I Change the Information I have Already given You?

You can always verify or request the removal of the personally identifiable information we have collected and change your registration information by selecting "Profile" from the main menu on the site.

## Do You Monitor Online Behavior?

This is a community site where the members communicate to share the information using our discussion boards. Also, our members communicate with each other through instant private messages. We do not, as a rule, monitor members' private message exchanges, but we reserve the right to do so if user is using our service for the purpose of solicitation or any other violation of our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

Member submissions that appear on the public area of the site are moderated and, if necessary, we reserve the right to edit, delete, remove or not use any communication on a public area of the site.

Members may choose to participate in community polls. The results of these polls do not reveal any personal identifiable information linked to the individual voters.

## What Security Features do You Have?

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). SSL is the leading security protocol on the Internet, it ensures that information being transferred over the network is private through a process called encryption. Once encrypted the information is an unintelligible code until it is decoded upon arrival at the authorized destination.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

All information about Advertisements and Advertising on SteadyHealth.com is strictly defined in [Advertising Policy](http://www.steadyhealth.com/polices/advertising/).

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

Steadyhealth.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are informed about any changes made.

### Contact

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or Steadyhealth.com Apps, please [Contact Us](http://www.steadyhealth.com/contact).

**Last updated on April, 17th 2012.**
